{
    "subject": "resource/August_Strindberg",
    "predicate": "ontology/notableWork",
    "object": "resource/The_Ghost_Sonata",
    "human_readable": "August Strindberg is notable for his work 'The Ghost Sonata'.",
    "questions": [
        {
            "score": 0.836881160736084,
            "question": "During what historical period did August Strindberg write 'The Ghost Sonata'?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.7028445601463318,
            "question": "Can you name another famous work by August Strindberg?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.6291500329971313,
            "question": "Is August Strindberg primarily known for his novels or plays?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.6045085787773132,
            "question": "What type of work is 'The Ghost Sonata'?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.5879648923873901,
            "question": "What are some common themes explored in August Strindberg's works?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.582974374294281,
            "question": "What is 'The Ghost Sonata' known for?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.3618616759777069,
            "question": "Who is the author of 'The Ghost Sonata'?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.3256088197231293,
            "question": "What are some critical perspectives on 'The Ghost Sonata'?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.30924540758132935,
            "question": "What impact did August Strindberg have on the literary world?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.2516626715660095,
            "question": "How is 'The Ghost Sonata' typically categorized (e.g., tragedy, comedy, drama)?"
        }
    ],
    "google_pages": [
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=August Strindberg is notable for his work 'The Ghost Sonata'.",
            "html": "dbpedia_8075_0.html"
        },
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=What impact did August Strindberg have on the literary world?",
            "html": "dbpedia_8075_1.html"
        },
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=What are some critical perspectives on 'The Ghost Sonata'?",
            "html": "dbpedia_8075_2.html"
        },
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=Who is the author of 'The Ghost Sonata'?",
            "html": "dbpedia_8075_3.html"
        }
    ],
    "selected_docs": [
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_8075_10.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_8075_19.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_8075_2.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_8075_4.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_8075_55.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_8075_59.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_8075_69.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_8075_7.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_8075_80.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_8075_9.txt"
        }
    ],
    "final_question": "Is true?",
    "responses": {
        "gemma2": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": "```json\n{'output': 'yes'}\n```  \n"
        },
        "llama3.1": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": "{\n  \"output\": \"yes\"\n}"
        },
        "qwen2.5": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": "```json\n{'output': 'yes'}\n```\n\nThe documents indeed mention that August Strindberg is known for \"The Ghost Sonata,\" supporting the statement that he is notable for his work in this play."
        },
        "mistral": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": " {\"output\": \"yes\"}"
        }
    },
    "need_tiebreaker": false,
    "tiebreakers_responses": {
        "qwen2.5:14b": {},
        "llama3.1:70b": {}
    },
    "final_decision": 1,
    "actual_decision": 1,
    "analysis": {
        "stratum": "Extremely Popular",
        "topic": "-"
    },
    "errors": {}
}